A fantasy adventure like no other
The Dark Kingdom is a fantasy, adventure, science
fiction film directed by Simon Wells.
To save their Kingdom from an army of undead, a group of warriors must travel through the
forbidden lands fighting the fearsome beasts that call The Dark Kingdom their home.
Richard, played by Ross O'Hennessy.
George, played by Ben Loyd-Holmes.
Princess Elizabeth, played by Rebecca Dyson-Smith.
Dimia, played by Zara Phythian.
Freya, played by Jemma Moore.
King Xalvador, played by Mike Mitchell.
In Darkness is a 2018 thriller film directed by Anthony
Byrne and written by Byrne and Natalie Dormer.
It stars Dormer, Ed Skrein, Emily Ratajkowski and Joely Richardson.
The film was released on 25 May 2018 in the United States by Vertical Entertainment
and on 6 July 2018 in the United Kingdom by Shear Entertainment.
The film explores themes of princess, fire, army, magic, kingdom.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.